

- Surrey, British Columbia, CA
- **+**1 672-515-1109
- github.com/amytang1234

Summary

An experienced Web Developer with a master degree in computer science and a recent diploma degree in Web Development from Lighthouse Labs. Highly skilled in coding using Javascript, HTML, and NodeJS for developing web applications. Interested in new technology and problem-solving.

Skills

Front-end: HTML, CSS, JS

Back-end: NodeJS, JSON, API, Postgres

Framework and Library: React, JQuery, Bootstrap, Axios, ExpressJS

Version Control: Git, Github

APIs: CRUD, REST

Programming languages: C, C#, JAVA, Python, VB, JS, Ruby

Education

Diploma 07/2021 - 10/2021

Lighthouse labs , Vancouver, BC

Web development

Master Degree 09/2004 - 06/2006

Fudan University, Shanghai, China

Software Engineer

Bachelor Degree 09/1995 - 07/1999

Harbin Institute of Technology, China

Computer Science

Volunteering

• Community Volunteer Income Tax Program (CVITP)

Assistant • Surrey 01/2019 - 03/2019

Volunteered over 3 hours per week with an organization helping with income tax

program

Tutoring • Python • South Surrey 02/2019 - 06/2019
Gave Python lessons to kids

Work experience

Student developer

07/2021 - 10/2021

Lighthouse labs

Successfully finished projects below,

TinyApp

A full stack web app built with Node and Express that allows users to shorten long URLs.(EJS, ExpressJS).

• Tweeter

A Single Page App (SPA) built with HTML, CSS, JS, ¡Query and AJAX, ExpressJS.

QuizApp

An app that lets you create quizzes and share them between friends. The creator of the quiz can view and share all the results at the end of the quiz. (NodeJS, Express -RESTful route, PostgreSQL for DBMSMS and git for version control)

• Interview Scheduler

A single page application (SPA), built using React, PostgreSQL database. The client application communicates with an API server over HTTP, using the JSON format

• Final group project- BudgetApp

The easy to use budgeting app that can be used to create budgets, and manage your expenses with Html ,CSS, ReactJS, Bootstrap, Axios, NodeJS, ExpressJS and PostgreSQL.

Software Engineer

09/2004 - 03/2008

Shanghai Etong network

- Involved in design, development and test of company's website
- Using c#, .NET framework distributed system

Instructor 09/1999 - 12/2015

Shanghai Normal university

- Taught the core courses of computer science such as Digital Circuit, Computer Organization, data structure, C programing, VB program, C#, etc.
- Instructed experiments of Digital Circuit, computer organization and programming in labs
- Supervised students about graduation projects